(Amy:)How long do you think
you can keep it from him?
(Bernadette:)Yeah, isn't it gonna get
worse the longer you wait?
(Penny:)Well, not necessarily.
(Penny:)You know,
Dad's not getting any younger,
(Penny:)so if I wait long enough,
(Penny:)I'll just tell him
he walked me down the aisle
(Penny:)and it was magical.
(Raj:)When did you learn
how to change a tire?
(Howard:)Every self-respecting gentleman
should know how
(Howard:)in case he comes across
a damsel in distress
(Howard:)by the side of the road.
(Sheldon:)If I see one scorpion,
(Sheldon:)I am getting
on someone's shoulders
(Sheldon:)and never coming down.
(Leonard:)And there's your damsel.
(Howard:)Wow, this one's really stuck.
(Raj:)Are you turning
it the right way?
(Sheldon:)No.
(Howard:)I took the other four off
(Howard:)and when I got to this one,
I thought,
"You know, I'm in a rut.
Let's shake things up."
(Raj:)Here, let me try.
(grunting)
(Raj:)You're right, it doesn't turn
the other way.